University - the best days of my life!
大学——我一生中最美好的时光！
I made lots of friends in my student dorm, went to great parties, joined the debating society… and, well, I did some work too - but I must confess my lecturers were very patient with my tardiness.
我在学生宿舍交了很多朋友，参加了精彩的派对，加入了辩论社……当然，我也做了一些功课——但我必须承认，我的讲师们对于我的拖拉非常宽容。
It's easy to look back at our university days through rose-tinted spectacles but the truth is that when we first arrived on campus, most of us were out of our comfort zone.
回顾大学时光，我们很容易把它想的过于乐观与美好，但事实是，当第一次来到校园时，我们中大多数人都离开了我们的舒适区。
In fact, a survey of students at Imperial College London has revealed that 3 out of 4 students experience high levels of stress, or a mental health condition, during their time at college.
事实上，伦敦帝国理工学院的一项调查显示，四分之三的学生在大学期间经历过高压或心理健康问题。
The survey, completed by over a thousand students, also found that 70% of those that experience stress do so at least once a week, and 9% of students feel stressed constantly.
这项由一千多名学生完成的调查还发现，70%的学生至少每周感到一次压力，9%的学生则经常不断地感到压力。
Kirsty, a student at Exeter University, didn't enjoy her first days in college.
埃克塞特大学的学生柯斯蒂（Kirsty）初期并不享受她的大学生活。
She says: "When I first got to university I don't think I'd realized that I'd forgotten how to make friends.
她说：“当我刚进入大学时，我并没有意识到我早已忘记如何交新朋友。
I'd been with the same school friends for seven years, and so I was trying to balance social success with academic success whilst learning how to look after myself at quite a young age."
之前的七年间，我一直和同校的朋友们在一起，所以我当时试图在平衡社交成功和学业成功的同时，还要学习如何在相当年轻的年纪照顾我自己。”
Dr Ruth Caleb of the counselling service at Brunel University in London has some tips that should make life easier for students before they set off for university.
伦敦布鲁内尔大学心理咨询服务的露丝·迦勒（Ruth Caleb）博士有一些建议，可以帮助学生在进入大学前让生活变得更轻松。
She says: "Certain things that I think it would be very helpful for students to have put in place are an ability to do the practical things of life – to do the washing, to do the cleaning and so on – being able to cook.
她说：“我认为有一些事情是对学生非常有帮助的，就是具备生活实践能力——比如洗衣服、打扫卫生等等——以及会做饭。
Budgeting is extremely important in university life."
预算管理在大学生活中非常重要。”
And Caleb adds: "You should learn how to spend time on your own comfortably."
迦勒还补充道：“你应该学会如何怡然自得地独处。”
I graduated and learnt how to take care of myself the hard way.
我毕业了，并通过很痛苦的方式学会了如何照顾自己。
I hope that new students these days remember to acquire some life skills before they make the big jump.
我希望如今的新生在迈出这重要一步之前，记得掌握一些生活技能。